

HARSH BHARGAVA

Graphic Designer and 3D Artist

ABOUT

I'm Harsh Bhargava, a self-Motivated And creative Graphic Designer specializes in Graphic Designing and 3D modelling and texturing. Through my work, I strive to Contribute to the World of Graphics, That can help inspire people's creativity and imagination. I am ready to channel and develop my skills into a career and prove Valuable in this Industry. I look forward to helping bring innovative ideas and practices and being a part of some exciting projects. My skills include: Social media posts, Thumbnails, brochure, Banner, Branding, logos and 3d graphics. Experienced in using photoshop, illustrator, premiere pro, Autodesk maya, Zbrush, substance painet, marmoset etc.

EXPERIENCE

06/2022 - 09/2022 3d Generalist Agrostar

01/2023 - 06/2023 3d Graphic designer (thedschool)

12/2023 - 04/2024 Graphic designer(virtucrop)

EDUCATION

09/2021 - 09/2024 Bachelor of Business Administration

- BBA

Indira Institute of Management, Pune

Arena Animation

CONTACT ME



ADDRESS

B 102,stanza mhada near lakshmi chowk punawale, Pune (MH),India



WEB

Gmail: harshbhargava2@gmail.com



PHONE 9752944209

SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

GRAPHIC DESIGNING

PREMIERE PRO

AFTER EFFECT

AUTODESK MAYA

MARMOSET TOOLBAG 4

SUBSTANCE PAINTER

ZBRUSH

3D MODELLING AND TEXTURING

3D PRODUCT ANIMATION